Morioh Radio, here,
ready with our next segment.
"Help! Midnight Mentor!"
Our first letter is from
"Forever 21, Pretty Baby."
"Kai, get a load of this.
I was late to my little rendezvous
again because of that thing.
Yeah, the one by the station!
The crossing that
never opens!
Ugh, it just goes ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding… It's so annoying!"
Now, just take it easy, Pretty Baby.
Oh…
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
See ya.
You serious?
EPISODE 7
TOSHIKAZU HAZAMADA (SHOW OFF)
So we're not the only
Stand users at school?
You got it. This is Toshikazu Hazamada,
a junior from Group-C.
Apparently this Hazamada guy
got in a spat
with his buddy over something
trivial right before spring.
Seems he dissed his
favorite idol or anime or something.
That night, all of a sudden, the friend
he was arguing with
gouged out his own left eye
with a mechanical pencil.
Crazy, right?
Rumor has it, Hazamada's friend
uttered these words while in the hospital:
"When I came to, I was staring at
my eyeball with the only eye I had left."
So you're saying this guy ripped out
his friend's left eye with
some kind of a Stand?
Maybe that's what happened,
maybe not.
Remember, the average person
can't see Stands.
I don't know,
this all sounds fishy to me.
What'd you say?!
Josuke, you've got no right
to say that to me!
I've got a real job now, y'know!
Huh? You're actually working?
'Course, Master Koichi!
I landed myself a little gig in finance.
Finance?
You don't mean loan shark, do you?
Well… Let's just say I'm
working with some good people!
That's great,
but did you forget about this?
Wait, Josuke!
M-Master Koichi!
You're going, too?
Just let that jackass,
Josuke, take care of it.
Something terrible's taking over my town.
And if Morioh's in danger,
then Mom, Dad, Sis,
and everyone else I care about
are in danger, too.
I'm scared,
but something has to be done!
W…
Wow, what a gutsy thing to say.
I'd expect nothing less from my hero!
But…
You'll have to excuse me
as I've got to go home now!
Stay out of trouble, Master Koichi!
Yeah, totally.
He doesn't seem to be in here.
But if that Hazamada guy can
act like nothing ever happened
after digging out
his friend's eye with a pencil,
then he must be one helluva creeper.
HAZAMADA
H-Hey, Josuke!
I'm gonna take a quick look
through this guy's locker.
Keep an eye out, Koichi.
Give me some warning next time!
All right… So he left his bag in here.
So he's still at school. Be careful.
R-Right.
Looks like he's in
the tennis club and a manga fan.
One thing's for sure,
this guy's got way too much shit.
I don't see how that bow and arrow
could be in here…
The hell is this wooden thing?
A Sta—
N-Nah… Looks like
it's an ordinary object.
So he's got one of those wooden
mannequins they sell in art stores?
That scared the crap out of me…
Huh?!
What? How?!
As soon as I touched
the thing, it turned into me.
Well, that pretty much proves it…
Hazamada's a Stand user!
Ah, great…
Turning into yours truly…
That's quite the cheeky move, pal…
You know the manga Perman, right?
I-It speaks!
It sounds and talks just like him!
You know, the copy robot in Perman?
Pretty useful, dontcha think?
Makes you wish you had one,
am I right?
Hey, Koichi…
What's this guy mumbling about?
Who the hell's Perman?
You don't know Perman?!
I'm shocked.
You sure you're Japanese?
All right, enough!
I'll be asking the questions around here!
M-My arm!
Josuke!
But my robot…
is one you won't want around.
Once it copies you,
you'll be making all the same movements.
Which means it's not a puppet.
It's a puppet master!
K-Koichi! Watch out!
Koichi!
And another one bites the dust…
Oh, but I didn't touch him.
The culprit is you, his dear friend.
It's shit like that…
that really makes my blood boil.
Making others do your dirty work,
cause you don't have
the balls to do it yourself.
Nothing makes me want
to kick ass more!
Well, great. Tee-hee!
Looks like you're out of range.
If you can't get any closer,
neither can your Stand.
In other words,
as long as I keep my distance,
Josuke, you don't have
a prayer against me!
My Stand's name is Show Off.
Possessing the doll has given
my Stand physical form…
Therefore any ordinary person can see it.
Hazamada! You sneaky…
My objective is simple:
Beat Jotaro within an inch of his life,
and make sure he
never returns to this town.
Pathetic outsider…
Snooping around and getting
in our business.
Although I did hear
Jotaro's Star Platinum
can stop time for
a couple of seconds.
There's not a single
Stand user among us
who can get anywhere close
to him.
That is, Josuke, no one besides the Stand
that just copied you now!
Time to render you unconscious,
meddlesome McCoy!
Squished it, huh?
The sound is sublime, isn't it?
Now, as long as you didn't sever the nerve,
you might be able to see again…
If you're lucky.
He'll be out for a while.
Well, that was easy.
All right! Carry my bag.
It's time to hunt Jotaro.
Piece of cake.
I'm pretty sure Jotaro's hotel is…
Uh…
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
Yeah, that's it.
K-Koichi!
Koichi!
J-Josuke, are you okay?
Fine, thanks…
Man, you sure've got plenty of spunk.
You're all busted up…
And still managed
to get him with your Stand.
What are you talking about?
That's only because,
the moment you sent me flying,
you healed my fractures
with Shining Diamond.
And, uh…
it'd be nice if you could heal
the injuries I got from breaking down
the door and window, too.
R-Right!
Hello, you've reached
the Morioh Grand Hotel.
Oh, uh, could you put me through
to Jotaro Kujo in Room 324?
Certainly
Come on! We've got to
tell Jotaro about that Stand!
Thank you for waiting.
The line for Room 324 is busy
Please try again later.
It's busy?
What?!
Of course! It must be the copy!
It got a hold of him before I could!
Are you sure, Josuke?
There's another Stand user
at your school?
Yep! I'll fill you in at Morioh Station.
Meet me at the square out in front.
Fifteen minutes is all it takes.
Got it.
See you in front of the station in fifteen.
Easy as pie.
Shit! He's not answering!
He must've left!
They must've baited Jotaro
to meet somewhere!
Damn!
All we can do now is go after the copy!
I really couldn't tell you two apart!
Yeah.
Well, what really freaks me out
are his fingers, not his face.
How often do you catch a glimpse of
your own fingers compared with your face?
I realized he'd copied
me down to my fingerprints.
Oh!
Josuke, you're early.
Where's Master Koichi?
H-Hazamada?!
What are you doing here?
Tamami Kobayashi?
So you really have no idea
why we're hanging out together?
N-No, I don't…
No clue whatsoever?
No! Why?!
Well then…
Good!
Step on it.
If we don't catch up
with Hazamada fast,
Jotaro's gonna be in deep shit!
SHOW OFF
TIME TO MEETING: 9 MINUTES
We can't let Jotaro meet the copy!
It'll be a disaster!
Yeah.
I haven't figured out
a solution just yet.
So for now, we run!
Bye-bye, Josuke!
See you tomorrow!
Bye!
Josuke!
Bye, Josuke!
Why the hell are they saying
goodbye only to you?
No one ever says that to me!
Whatever! Every girl in
this school is butt ugly, anyway!
Josuke…
Um, could you read this?
B-Bye.
What're you accepting notes
from her for?
Tear that thing up now!
Goddammit…
What the hell makes you so special?!
What does it matter now?
Wha…
I don't think you have time
to dilly dally.
How dare you speak to me that way?!
Ow!
You scraped your hand?
That was stupid.
I'm wood, 'member?
Shut up! Quit crowding me!
Dammit, he's really starting
to get under my skin.
This always happens with my Stand
Like when I copied my crush,
Junko, just the other day..
She was a complete bitch!
I couldn't take it,
so the whole thing was a flop.
Is there no one halfway decent
on this miserable planet? Shit!
Damn Josuke!
I'll take care of that Jotaro first.
I'll smash him to smithereens!
This is gonna be good!
My motorcycle!
He just ruined the coat!
Damn, dumb-ass!
He's dead!
Hey, take it easy,
it was probably an accident.
'Sides, he'll hear you.
You think I care?!
I want him to hear me!
Walking around like that…
Asshole!
He looks like a dying cricket.
That's a good one! I like it!
Yeah? Think it was good, huh?
Huh? What?
Keep a grip on him, Show Off.
I'll settle the score myself.
Wh-What are you doing, you freak?
Now don't worry yourself with
silly things like that.
Relax, and I'll make sure
you never have to open
that mouth again.
S-Stop!
A piece of glass?
J-Josuke Higashikata?!
Shit… And that shrimp, too?
Hazamada!
We finally caught up with you, asshole!
But did you forget?
Come face to face with my Show Off,
and become
an instant puppet, Josuke!
Control him, Show Off!
Don't be so sure.
Wha… What's happening…
That shard wasn't for hitting you…
It was to put it back in
its rightful place!
M-My right hand!
It turned back into wood!
This isn't good, Hazamada!
Settle down!
Pretend you're resting your hand
in your pocket!
No one will know!
We've got a bigger problem…
Jotaro should be almost at
the station by now!
As much as I'd like to
get rid of Josuke…
we don't have time
to go after him now!
H-Hazamada! Wait for me!
I see…
So they're meeting in
front of the station.
J-Josuke, we don't have
time to just hang around!
That road they just took is
the fastest way to the station!
And that's why I've got you, Koichi.
Guess Josuke's run into some trouble.
See Josuke anywhere?
Nope.
If I so much as glance at him,
he'll be my puppet in a flash.
Don't worry!
Hazamada! A train's coming.
It's the crossing that
never lets you through!
It'll cost us at least a minute or two…
All right!
We cross through the station!
NO CROSSING
Even if he's caught up with us,
Josuke won't get past that train!
One minute left!
We're gonna make it
to the meeting spot first!
I win!
Huh?
That's Josuke!
Wh-What about the train?!
Why's the crossing open?!
Hazamada, look!
Wh-What the hell kind of Stand is that?!
Great!
Ya see? That's why I've got you.
Ah! There he is!
J-Jotaro! It's me, Josuke!
Hey.
We made it!
We got Hazamada good,
didn't we, Josuke?
Something happen?
A copy?
A Stand that copied you
down to your fingerprints?
Yes!
Had he arrived before us,
who knows what would've happened?
But now we can relax.
That copying bastard's missing
his hand, so it'll be easy.
I made sure to do
a number on his right hand.
You can use that to tell us apart.
All right.
They should be here any moment now.
Huh? What am I doing with this?
Why did I take a pen
out of Jotaro's pocket?
I-I can't move!
My arm just stopped moving!
The other side of the glass…
Th-That's…
Josuke Higashikata…
You're gonna plunge that pen
into Jotaro's brain,
killing him instantly!
After all, if he's left alive,
your Shining Diamond will only heal him.
Josuke!
Your meddling is the cause of all this!
I was only going to beat Jotaro up
and chase him out of town.
But now,
Jotaro's gonna die by your hand!
This whole thing is your fault!
Now!
Slaughter him, Show Off!
J- Jotaro…
Bastard!
Something the matter, Josuke?
Huh? No…
Fortunately for me,
it looks like those guys
finally tracked down Hazamada.
Little turd!
It's just like that Josuke guy said…
You were across
the overpass at the station.
He's a real swell guy.
He treated our wounds and,
how, I'll never know,
he completely fixed 'em!
I think it's time we paid
you back for your little stunt earlier.
There's something out behind
the bathroom we've gotta show ya.
Once it gets you,
that Stand is pretty scary.
Well, suppose I should mutilate
this doll now.
I could use a little pick-me-up.
Meanwhile, Tamami was…
hospitalized, unbeknownst to everyone.
What a fool!
My condolences.
EPISODE 8
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 1